



Almir Hrštić

O Home: 38173, Sickte, Germany

Email: almirhrstic@gmail.com Phone: (+49) 15223760188

Gender: Male **Date of birth:** 26/03/1995 **Nationality:** Bosnian-Herzegovinian

ABOUT ME

I officially began my journey in late 2016 when I enrolled in a technical university, acquiring theoretical knowledge. Meanwhile, I embarked on a student internship, which provided me with practical experience. Later, I transitioned into full-time work, taking on numerous responsibilities. I am now exploring new opportunities, with a focus on frontend development and CMS.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

[09/2010 - 05/2014] **Technician**

Co-educational High School "Hasan Kikić" msshkg.co.ba

City: Gradačac

Country: Bosnia and Herzegovina Field(s) of study: Electrical Engineering

[09/2016 - 05/2020]

Bachelor Engineer

American University in Bosnia and Herzegovina aubih.edu

City: Tuzla

Country: Bosnia and Herzegovina

Field(s) of study: Information Technology

WORK EXPERIENCE

[09/2018 - 05/2019] **Front-end Developer**

StarNet starnet.co.ba

City: Tuzla

Country: Bosnia and Herzegovina

Internship, part-time and in a remote environment. Integrated segments of a Bootstrap theme using Aurelia framework for enhanced reusability.

[09/2019 - 05/2020]

Full-stack Developer

Leftor leftor.com

City: Tuzla

Country: Bosnia and Herzegovina

Internship, part-time and in a hybrid environment. Established IMS and CAS as in-house solutions using React, Bootstrap and Laravel frameworks.

[09/2020 - 08/2023] **WordPress Developer**

Imel imel.ba City: Lukavac

Country: Bosnia and Herzegovina

Full-time and in a hybrid environment. Developed custom-tailored solutions via WordPress platform and various client-side technologies.

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Bosnian

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING C1 READING C1 WRITING C1

SPOKEN PRODUCTION C1 **SPOKEN INTERACTION** C1

German

LISTENING A1 READING A1 WRITING A1

SPOKEN PRODUCTION A1 SPOKEN INTERACTION A1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user